Sometimes I think how lucky I am.
My husband brings food and drinks
for me without even asking.  What more could a woman
want?  Here Aru's father
brought samosa chaat for me.  I
hid the chaat in the kitchen and Aru was taking it
saying that she also wanted it as it was kept in the kitchen.  Please bring it to me, I am
telling you
no son it is finished.  But what can be done
?  Since he troubled me so much, I had to
feed him too.  Aru's father was
bringing it for me secretly.  But Aru
saw it all.  So now that I have seen it brother, I will have to
give it to him.  She had just finished the chaat and
sat down.  By then all my parcels had
arrived.  Aru's father had ordered something for me.  I am
saying that he does everything for me without saying anything.
A few days ago I was
crying and telling Aru's father that a
lot of my hair was falling.  So Aaru
's father has got Pros Care
hair growth serum for me because it reduces hair fall.
I use it daily and I am
getting very good results.  And
it is also available on Flipkart and Amazon.
And by applying this my hair is
growing a lot.